We’re Identical Fucking Twins!
Dicks: The Musical is a music, comedy film directed by Larry Charles.
Two self-obsessed businessmen discover they're long-lost identical twins and come
together to plot the reunion of their eccentric divorced parents.
Craig, played by Josh Sharp.
Trevor, played by Aaron Jackson.
Harris, played by Nathan Lane.
Evelyn, played by Megan Mullally.
God, played by Bowen Yang.
Gloria, played by Megan Thee Stallion.
Dicks: The Musical is a 2023 American musical comedy film directed by Larry Charles, based on the off-Broadway
musical Fucking Identical Twins by Josh Sharp and Aaron Jackson, who helped adapt the film.
The film stars Megan Mullally, Megan Thee Stallion, Bowen Yang, Nathan Lane, Aaron Jackson, and Josh
Sharp, with Tom Kenny and Frank Todaro appearing in supporting roles as the Sewer Boys.
It tells the story of a pair of identical twins who plot to
reunite their divorced parents as narrated by God.
The film had its world premiere at the 2023 Toronto
International Film Festival on September 7, 2023.
On October 6, 2023, it was released in the United States
by A24 as the studio's first musical film.
The film explores themes of musical, based on play or
musical, twin brother, crude humor, twins.
The tone is lighthearted.